[
    {
        "question": "Q1: Who developed the bootstrap?",
        "a":"James Gosling",
        "b":"Mark Jukervich",
        "c":"Dennis Ritchie",
        "d":"Mark Otto and Jacob Thornton",
        "ans":"ans4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q2: Is Bootstrap3 mobile-first?",
        "a":"True",
        "b":"False",
        "c":"Can't say",
        "d":"May be",
        "ans":"ans1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q3: Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to provide a responsive fixed width container?",
        "a":".container-fixed",
        "b":".container-fluid",
        "c":".container",
        "d":"All of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q4: How many columns are allowed in a bootstrap grid system?",
        "a":"2",
        "b":"12",
        "c":"3",
        "d":"5",
        "ans":"ans2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q5: Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create a big box for calling extra attention?",
        "a":".box",
        "b":".container",
        "c":".container-fluid",
        "d":".jumbotron",
        "ans":"ans4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q6: Which of the following class is used to create a black navigation bar?",
        "a":".navbar-default",
        "b":".navbar-inverse",
        "c":".navbar-black",
        "d":".navbar-dark",
        "ans":"ans2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q7: The plugin used to create a cycle through elements as a slideshow is -",
        "a":"slideshow",
        "b":"scrollspy",
        "c":"carousel",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q8: Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create a big box for calling extra attention?",
        "a":".box",
        "b":".container",
        "c":".container-fluid",
        "d":".jumbotron",
        "ans":"ans4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q9: Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to create a dropdown menu?",
        "a":".dropdown",
        "b":".select",
        "c":".select-list",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q10:  Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to create a basic list group?",
        "a":".grouped-list",
        "b":".select-list",
        "c":".list-group",
        "d":".list-grouped",
        "ans":"ans3"
    }
]